ALEJANDRO SEDANO



Personal Data

Date of Birth: 23 June 1987

Address:

Senatorska 40/99 00-095 Warsaw, Poland

Mobile:

+48 510 383 877

E-mail:

alejandro@sedano.me

Website:

http://sedano.me

Languages Spanish Native English (C2) Full professional proficiency Polish (B1) Working proficiency German (A2) Limited working proficiency **Skills** Programming **JavaScript** Python FEA Bootstrap Visual Basic LaTeX Software MS Office CAD Project **VS** Code **Chrome Dev Tools** Inkscape SolidWorks Engineering GD&T 3D Printing Robotics **Product Development** ISO 13485 FDA Medical Devices **Project Management**

I'm a Robotics Engineer with experience in both technical and project management fields. I have worked for recognized Applied Robotics Research Institutes and lead Projects in the food and medical sectors. I have global awareness by having lived and worked in four different countries in Europe and America. I'm passionate about technology and a web developer in my free time.

EXPERIENCE

07/2014- Present	Project Engineer / European Engineering Leadership Programme Mars Incorporated, Poland Working on technically-complex projects in the food industry that involve breakthrough technology and leadership skills.
03/2013- 12/2013	Robotics Research Assistant Fraunhofer-Gesellschaft, Germany Mechanical design, modeling, construction, and testing of robotic systems for modular musculoskeletal robots.
09/2009- 08/2011	Validation and Development Engineer Tecnologia y Diseño Industrial, Mexico Design, testing, validation and documentation of orthopedic medical devices under strict medical regulations such as ISO 13485 and FDA.

EDUCATION

10/2012- 09/2013	Warsaw University of Technology, Poland Master in Automation and Robotics Faculty of Power and Aeronautical Engineering Achievement: Summa Cum Laude
09/2011- 08/2012	Ecole Centrale de Nantes, France Master in Automation, Robotics and Applied Informatics
08/2005- 07/2010	Universidad Panamericana, Mexico Bachelor in Mechatronics Engineering Specialization in Systems Optimization Achievement: Top student in class

PROJECTS

Project	ViveroelJardin.mx	Myorobotics
Description	Own eCommerce start-up	Lightweight, 3D printed robotics
Function	Web Development	Robotic Design and Construction
Project Description Function	Robot Programming Editor VAL parser and text editor Design and Implementation of UI	Robotic Hand Prosthesis Low cost robotic arm prototype Controls and Programming

HOBBIES

Travelling, Computers, Videogames, Internet of Things.

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in my application to be processed for the purposes of the recruitment process under the Personal Data Protection Act as of 29 August 1997, consolidated text: Journal of Laws 2002, item 1182 as amended.